<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!--
text.xml file from Click to chat app by TrianguloY.
Permission given to translate only.

Instructions for manual translation:
- Translate the properties making sure not to overpass the maximum character number.
- Currently this file is copied manually, line breaks are kept and no need to scape special characters.

If you added/modified the following file add your name here to give credit:


 -->
<parameters>

    <!-- Preferably use the name from https://faq.whatsapp.com/general/chats/how-to-use-click-to-chat/ in your language -->
    <title max_chars="50">Click to chat [small, no ads]</title>

    <description_short max_chars="80">Open a WhatsApp chat from any number (you and that number).</description_short>

    <!-- Don't forget to add your name in the list at the bottom (please keep the names as they are).-->
    <description_long max_chars="4000">
Disclaimer: This app is not affiliated with nor endorsed by WhatsApp Inc.
Previous name: "Open in WhatsApp (click to chat)", changed to comply with WhatsApp guidelines.
------------------

'What is this app used for?' The answer is often misunderstood: you can open a chat on the official WhatsApp app (or Business) with another user if you know their number. This app replaces the method of saving the number into contacts. This will NOT allow you to 'spy other conversations', 'contact with numbers without WhatsApp', 'hide your number' or other crazy things. This is the same as clicking an unknown number on a group, creating manually the url link or saving the contact.

'Why should I use this instead of others?' You are free to choose of course! This app only has the 'open in WhatsApp' feature and improvements, but for this reason the app is extremely simple and so I made it without ads, as small a possible, and free; just to help others use this feature that WhatsApp have (note that I'm not affiliated with WhatsApp Inc). Since I published it the popularity increased as unexpected (thanks!) and other apps with the same functionality (some even blatant copies without my permission) have populated the store. You can use whichever you prefer, but this one is (last time I checked at least) the smallest of all, the only one add-free, and the only one without 'dangerous' permissions (not internet, not storage, nothing. Check it! ).

-------------------

This app uses WhatsApp 'click to chat' feature (https://faq.whatsapp.com/en/android/26000030/) to open a chat with any number (a chat between you and that number).
No contact is created on the device, you don't need to save it on your contacts list. Just open the app, enter the number, click the button and the chat will open (if the number doesn't exists WhatsApp will notify it).

Useful on situations like:
- Someone called you and you want to contact it via WhatsApp?
- You need to send a message to someone but you don't want to save it?
- You want to start a chat with yourself?

Prefix:
You need to specify the prefix of the number, even if from your own country (will be kept when reopening the app). You can enter it manually or tap the + button to choose from a list.

Create links:
You can create an url link that will open WhatsApp on the specified number. This is a WhatsApp feature, you don't need this app to open the link, only to create it.
You can also add a message that will be autocompleted (will NOT, I repeat, will NOT be sent, the user must press the send button manually).
If you specify a message but not a number WhatsApp will ask who to send it to (again, will NOT be sent, only autocompleted).
You can save the link as a quick shortcut, share it so people can contact you (the number is visible on the link, be careful), set a predefined message on a site to 'share it on WhatsApp', etc. Remember, you don't need this app to open the link, it is handled by WhatsApp.
Hidden shortcut: long tap the 'share' button to quickly copy the link to the clipboard.

Recents list:
When a number is opened it is saved on a recents list, in case you want to open a number again
and you don't remember the number. You can also pin numbers and name them, or even create
shortcuts.

---------------------------

This is a tool app: simple and lightweight. No extra features, no extra size, no dangerous
permissions, no ads...just the open-in-WhatsApp feature (with each update I add a little related
feature, but I want to keep it as simple and lightweight as possible).

Translation:
Thanks to Timofey Lisunov, Matheus Damacs, Yusuf Emen, Benjamin Yılmaz Çetiner, Richard Anderson
(Hirai RCD), Aditya, Armand Secco, Yoni Cohen jonbir3, MageshBabu K (mage1k99), artmann (Dwi
Legowo), Steven Felix and mezysinc for the translations!

Permissions used:
SHORTCUT: To create shortcuts in the launcher.
-Nothing else- (they aren't necessary)

Apk size:
~100 KB (0,1MB)
    </description_long>

    <!-- Not needed if you don't translate the changelog -->
    <changelog_footer>Do you like the update? Suggestions? You can say so in the comments or in the blog! https://triangularapps.blogspot.com/</changelog_footer>
</parameters>